const questions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "Which national team does Thibaut Courtois play for?",
      options: ["France", "Belgium", "Netherlands"],
      correctAnswer: "Belgium",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "Which club did Achraf Hakimi play for before joining PSG?",
      options: ["Chelsea", "Inter Milan", "Barcelona"],
      correctAnswer: "Inter Milan",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "Which club did Manchester City sign Rúben Dias from?",
      options: ["Porto", "Benfica", "Sporting CP"],
      correctAnswer: "Benfica",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "Which club signed William Saliba before Arsenal?",
      options: ["Marseille", "Saint-Étienne", "Lyon"],
      correctAnswer: "Saint-Étienne",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Alphonso Davies was born in which country?",
      options: ["Canada", "Liberia", "USA"],
      correctAnswer: "Liberia",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "Which position does Rodri mainly play?",
      options: ["Attacking midfielder", "Center-back", "Defensive midfielder"],
      correctAnswer: "Defensive midfielder",
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "Which club did Jude Bellingham play for before Real Madrid?",
      options: ["Dortmund", "Bayern Munich", "RB Leipzig"],
      correctAnswer: "Dortmund",
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "Which Premier League club did Kevin De Bruyne play for earlier?",
      options: ["Arsenal", "Chelsea", "Tottenham"],
      correctAnswer: "Chelsea",
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "Salah became a global star after playing for which Italian club?",
      options: ["Juventus", "Napoli", "Roma"],
      correctAnswer: "Roma",
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "Which club did Haaland play for before Manchester City?",
      options: ["RB Salzburg", "Borussia Dortmund", "Ajax"],
      correctAnswer: "Borussia Dortmund",
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "Vinícius Júnior joined Real Madrid from which club?",
      options: ["Santos", "Flamengo", "Palmeiras"],
      correctAnswer: "Flamengo",
    },
  ];
  
  export default questions;
